hasbrolab.com 2019-07-10

# HasLab Privacy Policy

(Last Updated: 2/15/2018)

#### WELCOME!

This privacy policy (" **Privacy Policy** ") explains how Hasbro, Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliated companies that operate within the United States (collectively, "Hasbro", "we", "our", or "us") collect, use and disclose your information when you visit our websites and other online products and services that are not directed to children or otherwise intended for use by children (collectively, the " **Hasbro Services** "). Please be sure to review Hasbro's [Privacy Policy for Child-Directed Websites](https://www.hasbro.com/en-us/privacy) to learn more about our privacy practices on our child-targeted and general audience websites and Hasbro's [Mobile Privacy Policy](http://www.hasbro.com/app_esrb_privacy) or  [Cast-Enabled Application Privacy Policy](http://www.hasbro.com/en-us/privacy-connectedtv) to learn more about our privacy practices in relation to mobile application usage. 

This Privacy Policy and the ESRB certification seals shown on the Hasbro Services confirm that Hasbro is a valid licensee, and participating member, of the [Entertainment Software Rating Board's Privacy Certified Program](http://www.esrb.org/privacy/faq.aspx#10) (" **ESRB Privacy Certified** "). To protect your privacy, we have voluntarily undertaken this privacy initiative and have had all of the Hasbro Services where this Privacy Policy is posted reviewed and certified by ESRB Privacy Certified to meet established online information collection, use, and disclosure practices. As a licensee of this privacy program, we are subject to frequent audits of the Hasbro Services and other enforcement and accountability mechanisms administered independently by the ESRB. 

We ask that you take the time to read this Privacy Policy carefully. By using the Hasbro Services, you agree to this Privacy Policy. 

 _If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Hasbro Services_

. 

### TABLE OF CONTENTS

  1.   NOTE TO USERS
  2.   Changes to this Privacy Policy
  3.   What information is collected from me?
  4.   How does Hasbro use my information?
  5.   With whom does Hasbro share my personal information?
  6.   What are my information choices?
  7.   Security
  8.   Your California Privacy Rights
  9.   Contact Us

### 1\. NOTE TO USERS

**_The Hasbro Services are not intended for children under 13 and we do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from children under 13 in connection with the Hasbro Services._** If you believe that we may have unintentionally collected your and/or your child's personal information, you may contact us at: 

Hasbro, Inc.  
Attn: Hasbro Services Administrator  
1027 Newport Avenue, Mailstop A906  
Pawtucket, RI 02861  
(800) 255-5516  

For any other issue, please contact [Hasbro Consumer Care](https://corporate.hasbro.com/en-us/consumer-care). We will be happy to take your request. Please note that any personal information provided by you to us via our customer support website is subject to the privacy policy and terms of use of that website. Please read those documents before providing any personal information to us via our customer support website. 

Back to top

### 2\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy whenever you access the Hasbro Services to make sure that you understand our information collection, use and disclosure practices. We may change the provisions of this Privacy Policy at any time and will indicate when changes have been made by revising the date at the top of this Privacy Policy. Your use of the Hasbro Services, or any portion thereof, following the posting of such changes shall constitute your consent to such changes. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will provide you with additional notice of such changes by sending you an email at the last email address that you provided us, or by prominently posting notice of the changes on the applicable website(s). 

 _If you do not agree with the changes we make to this Privacy Policy, please stop using the Hasbro Services._

Back to top

### 3\. WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED FROM ME?

#### INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE

Hasbro may collect information that you provide when you use the Hasbro Services, such as when you: 

(1) create an account or subscribe to the Hasbro Services;  
(2) make a purchase or request to purchase a product;  
(3) participate in contests, events or promotions;  
(4) send questions or comments via email or live chat to Hasbro customer support;  
(5) fill out online surveys;  
(6) sign up for our newsletter or other email alerts;  
(7) share a website with a friend;  
(8) share a news release through our investor website;  
(9) submit your resume to us online; or  
(10) otherwise communicate with us through the Hasbro Services. 

Depending on the activity, the types of personal information that you provide may include: 

(1) your first and/or last name;  
(2) email address;  
(3) telephone number;  
(4) address (including billing address and/or shipping address);  
(5) credit card or other payment information; and  
(6) other contact or identifying information that you choose to provide. 

Non-personal information you may also provide includes your birth date, gender, toy and game ownership and preferences, company name, and job title. When you provide this information at the same time as you provide certain personal information (e.g., your name or other contact or identifying information), we may combine these data points. Standing alone, these pieces of non-personal information we collect cannot be used to identify or directly contact you. However, when we combine your non-personal information with your personal information, it may become personally identifiable (e.g., first and last name combined with birth date). 

In some cases, we also collect information you provide about others, such as when you refer someone to the Hasbro Services (including promotions) or when you purchase and ship products to someone. We will use this information to fulfill your requests and will not send communications to your contacts unrelated to your requests, unless they separately consent to receive communications from us. 

**Please note that this Privacy Policy applies to any information we collect when you use the Hasbro Services. If the Hasbro Services collect and/or share personal information in a manner that differs from what is described in this Privacy Policy, we will use reasonable efforts to notify you of the purposes for which such information will be collected and/or with whom such information will be shared (if applicable), whether via a just-in-time notification at the point of collection or via an alternate notice.**

#### INFORMATION WE COLLECT AUTOMATICALLY FROM YOU

When you access or use the Hasbro Services, we may also automatically collect information about your visit. For example, when you visit our websites, we collect your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, and may also collect other unique identifiers (e.g., ad tags), information about your hardware, operating system version, browser type and language, screen resolution, geographic location (country, state, and city level), the URL of the website you visited before navigating to the Hasbro Services, and other non-personal analytics and statistical data regarding you use of the websites (e.g., downloads, number of users, access times, sessions, page views, frequency of use, retention, clicks, etc.). In addition to the above, if you access the Hasbro Services via a mobile device, we may also collect your device ID, device make and model, and mobile carrier. 

To collect this information, we use various technologies, including the following: 

**Cookies** : Cookies are small data files stored on your computer or mobile device by a website. Among other things, cookies help us improve the Hasbro Services and your experience, see which areas and features of the Hasbro Services are popular, and count visits. For more information about cookies and how to disable them, please see  What are my information choices?" below. 

**Clear GIFs** : Clear GIFs, sometimes called "web bugs" or "web beacons," are small electronic images that are placed on a web page or in an email message. We use clear GIFs to monitor user behavior, deliver cookies, collect information, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness, and to tell if a recipient has opened and acted upon an email. 

**Log Files** : Log files record website activity on the Hasbro Services and enable us to gather statistics about our users' browsing habits. These entries help Hasbro determine (among other things) how many and how often users have accessed or used the Hasbro Services, which pages of the Hasbro Services they've visited, and other similar data. 

**Do Not Track (DNT) Signals** : Your browser may allow you to set a Do Not Track (DNT) signal indicating that you do not wish your online activity to be tracked. Currently, our system does not support and cannot act on DNT signal headers that we may receive. However, the choices that we provide you concerning collection and use of your personal information will continue to operate as described in this Privacy Policy. 

We may associate the information we collect from these technologies with other personal information that you provide for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. 

#### INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM THIRD PARTIES

We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect through the Hasbro Services. For example, if you create or log into your account through a third-party social networking site, we may have access to certain information from that site, such as your name, account information and friends, in accordance with the authorization procedures determined by such third-party social networking site. 

#### WEBSITE ANALYTICS

We use analytics services and software provided by third parties to help us understand how users access and use the Hasbro Services. These tools and services use cookies, web beacons and other devices or technologies on the Hasbro Services to enable them to track traffic data. The data collected typically includes information such as your IP address, your Internet Service Provider, your web browser, the time spent on web pages, the links clicked and the advertisements viewed on those pages. We use this information to improve the Hasbro Services and your experience, to see which areas and features of the Hasbro Services are popular, and to count visits. 

#### THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING

We engage third parties to place ads for our products and services on other websites and online services. These third parties use cookies, web beacons and other devices or technologies to collect information about your visits to websites and mobile applications, including Hasbro's websites and mobile applications. The data collected typically includes information such as your IP address, your web browser, web pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked and whether you purchased an advertised product. These third parties use this information to deliver advertising and/or content targeted to your interests. For more information about targeted advertising provided by these third parties, and how to opt-out of having your information used in this way by companies that participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA") or the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI"), please visit: www.aboutads.info/choices or www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. If you are a Pinterest user, you can opt-out of Pinterest's use of information about your web viewing activity to target ads to you through your personalization settings. Hasbro is not responsible for the effectiveness of, or compliance with, any third parties' opt-out options or programs or the accuracy of their statements regarding their opt-out options or programs. 

Back to top

### 4\. HOW DOES HASBRO USE MY INFORMATION?

#### USE OF INFORMATION

We use personal information collected through the Hasbro Services for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise disclosed to you on or in connection with the Hasbro Services. For example, we may use your information to: 

  * Send you advertising or promotional materials, including information about new products, contests, features and enhancements, special offers and other events of interest from Hasbro and our select partners; 
  * Operate and improve the Hasbro Services, including by linking or combining your information with other information we get from third parties; 
  * Provide and deliver the products and services you request, process transactions, and to send you related information, including confirmations and invoices; 
  * Send you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages; 
  * Respond to your comments, questions, and requests and provide customer service; 
  * Monitor performance of the Hasbro Services, overall usage of the Hasbro Services and user retention rates, track how users are engaging with the Hasbro Services, identify which website features are least and most utilized, identify problem areas within the websites, and inform design development for future updates; and 
  * Carry out any other purpose conveyed to you at the time the information was collected. 

Back to top

### 5\. WITH WHOM DOES HASBRO SHARE MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?

#### SHARING OF INFORMATION

We share information about you with third parties as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy or through the Hasbro Services, including: 

  * With your consent, including if we notify you through the Hasbro Services that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information; 
  * With third party vendors, consultants and other service providers who are working on our behalf and need access to your information to carry out their work for us. We require these entities to maintain the confidentiality, security, and integrity of the personal information they obtain from us; 
  * With our affiliates for internal business purposes; 
  * With our affiliates and third parties for Hasbro's own marketing purposes and those affiliates' and third parties' own business purposes, including direct marketing purposes (California residents have certain rights set forth in the section entitled "Your California Privacy Rights"); 
  * When we believe it is necessary or appropriate to: (i) comply with applicable law or legal process or to respond to lawful requests or legal authorities; (ii) protect the rights and property of Hasbro and our employees, agents, users and other third parties, including to enforce our agreements, policies and terms and conditions of use as provided on the Hasbro Service, and protect against fraudulent, abusive, inappropriate, or unlawful use of the Hasbro Services; and (iii) protect the safety of Hasbro, our users or any third party; and 
  * In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, bankruptcy or reorganization, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company. 

We may also share aggregated information or information that we have collected from you through the Hasbro Services, including on co-branded pages and where we have taken reasonable measures to de-identify such information. 

#### SOCIAL SHARING FEATURES

The Hasbro Services may offer third party social sharing features and other integrated tools (such as the Facebook widget), which let you share actions you take on the Hasbro Services with other media, and vice versa. The use of such features may enable the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the third party that provides these features. For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features, please visit the privacy policies of the third parties that provide these features. 

#### LINKING TO THIRD PARTY SITES

To provide relevant information not found on the Hasbro Services, to facilitate online shopping, and to allow you to interact with other websites and/or applications in which you may have accounts (such as Facebook and other social media sites), Hasbro may provide links or embed third-party applications that allow login from the Hasbro Services to third party websites. Your use of these third party websites and/or applications is subject to the third parties' privacy policies and terms of use, and we encourage you to read the third parties' privacy policies and terms of use before submitting personal or other information or using the websites and/or applications. 

#### MATCHED LIST ADS

Third party websites and applications may display ads from Hasbro that are targeted to reach people on those websites or applications who are also identified on one of more of Hasbro's databases. This is done by matching common factors between Hasbro's databases and the databases of these third parties. For instance, we may share your email address with Facebook as part of Facebook's matched list ad services. If we use Facebook's matched list ad services, you should be able to hover over the box in the right corner of the Facebook ad to find out how to opt-out with us from such list. If you opt-out with us from Facebook matched list ad services, we will remove the matching personal information from that Facebook list; however, this will not take effect immediately and if you have multiple emails or other accounts, you may have to opt-out separately for each one. We are not responsible for such third parties' failure to comply with your or our opt-out instructions. 

Back to top

### 6\. WHAT ARE MY INFORMATION CHOICES?

#### REGARDING PERSONAL INFORMATION

If you have registered with the Hasbro Services, you may at any time review and/or update the contact information we have for you or inform us that you want us to remove your information from our database, either by following the instructions provided on that particular Hasbro Service or by contacting [Hasbro Consumer Care](https://corporate.hasbro.com/en-us/consumer-care). If you choose to send us an email, please be sure to include the following in your message: the name of the website at which you registered and the email address you used to register so that we can verify your request. We will respond to all access requests as soon as possible. 

#### REGARDING COOKIES

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of the Hasbro Services. 

#### REGARDING PROMOTIONAL COMMUNICATIONS

You may opt-out of receiving promotional emails, text messages or mail from Hasbro by declining to receive such communications at the time of registration or at the time you otherwise provide the information to us. You may also opt-out of receiving promotional emails or text messages by following the instructions in those emails or text messages or by sending an email to  [Hasbro Consumer Care](https://corporate.hasbro.com/en-us/consumer-care). 

If you opt-out, we may still send you transactional or relationship messages, such as emails about your account or our ongoing business relations. 

### 7\. SECURITY

Hasbro has established policies in an effort to protect your personal information against loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and/or destruction. For example, Hasbro strives to provide only those employees performing a legitimate business function with access to users' personal information. Hasbro also reviews its security procedures periodically to consider appropriate new technology and updated methods. 

Hasbro retains your information for business purposes, for as long as your account is active, and/or as long as is reasonably necessary to provide you with our products and services. Hasbro will also retain your information as reasonably necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. We may also retain cached or archived copies of your information for a reasonable period of time. 

Despite our efforts, please be aware that no security measure is ever perfect or impenetrable. To that end, Hasbro will notify users of a data breach when Hasbro determines that is reasonably necessary in accordance with applicable law. 

Back to top

### 8\. YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

Since 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of this website who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information as defined by the statute to our affiliates and third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. For inquiries regarding our disclosure policy, please call or write us at: 

Hasbro, Inc.  
Attention: Website Administrator  
1027 Newport Avenue, Mailstop A906  
Pawtucket, RI 02861  
(800) 255-5516 

Back to top

### 9\. CONTACT US

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us using the following contact information: 

Hasbro, Inc.  
Attention: Website Administrator  
1027 Newport Avenue, Mailstop A906  
Pawtucket, RI 02861  
(800) 255-5516 

For any other issues, please contact [Hasbro Consumer Care](https://corporate.hasbro.com/en-us/consumer-care). For additional information about the Hasbro Services, please review the terms and conditions of use provided on the Hasbro Service. 

As aforementioned, Hasbro is a licensee of the ESRB's Privacy Certified Program. If you believe that we have not responded to your privacy-related inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, please contact ESRB at <https://www.esrb.org/privacy/contact.aspx> or: 

**ESRB**

Attn: Privacy Certified Program  
420 Lexington Avenue, Suite 2240  
New York, NY 10170  

Back to top
